Register of the Howard Palfrey Jones papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1934-1973 (Box 1-20)
  - Hotel Duta Indonesia, 1967
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1968
  - House Foreign Affairs Committee, 1969
  - Howard, Arthur L., 1966
  - Howard, Frances H., 1967-1968
  - Howard, John, 1964-1965
  - Howe, Arthur, Jr., 1965
  - Howell, Henry Adam, 1967-1968
  - Howland, Harold E., 1964-1969
  - Hoxie, R. Gordon, 1971
  - Hubbard, James C., 1968
  - Huben, Cal von, 1972
  - Huffman, Charles E., 1968
  - Hughes, Mildred, 1960-1964
  - Hughes, Robert H., 1968
  - Hughes, Thomas Lowe, 1967-1972
  - Humelsine, Carlisle H., 1964
  - Humphrey, George M., 1960
  - Hunter, John, 1966
  - Hurley, Thomas E., 1963
  - Hurst, Russell E., 1964-1965
  - Hurwick, Melvin A., 1971-1972
  - Hussey, William B., 1968
  - Hutasoit, Dr. and Mrs., 1966
  - Hutchins, Lt. Gen., C. E., Jr., 1968
  - Huth, Donald E., 1964
  - Huttrer, Charles P., 1968
  - Hutzel, John M., 1972
  - Hwang Chang Foong, 1965
  - Ikeda, Hayato, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Ikehara, Sadao, 1968
  - Ilott, Sir John, 1967
  - Indonesia House, 1965-1966
  - Indonesian-American Society, 1965-1971
  - Ingraham, Edward C., 1962-1972
  - Ingram, Donald, 1966
  - Inouye, Daniel K., 1968
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1966
  - Institute of International Education, 1964-1968
  - Institute of World Affairs, 1970
  - Inter-Continental Hotels, 1966
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1949
  - International Development Corp., 1970
  - International House, 1967
  - International Studies Association, 1968
  - International Union of Local Authorities, 1948
  - International Year Book and Statesmen's Who's Who, 1964
  - Irani, Marie, 1964-1972
  - Irwin, John N., II, 1971
  - Iskander, Otto, 1966-1967
  - Island Realty, North Haven Me., 1963
  - Ismael, Tan Sri, 1967
  - Istanto, Joseph F., 1966-1969
  - Isthmian Lines, Inc., 1966
  - Ito, Keiichi, 1967
  - Ivey, John E., Jr., 1965-1966
  - Jackson, Lura, 1968
  - Jackson, S. J., Jr., 1959
  - Jackson, W. Bart, 1969
  - Jacobsen, James, 1965
  - Jamieson, James P., 1962
  - Jandrey, Frederick, 1965-1967
  - Jansen, William H., 1964-1965
  - Jennings, Peter, 1965-1966
  - Jennings, Mrs. Robert, 1966
  - Jensen, Daniel L., 1969
  - John Day Co., Inc., 1964
  - Johnson, Dallas, 1968-1971
  - Johnson, Ladd I., 1962-1971
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964-1967
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B., 1966
  - Johnson, Mrs. Ralph, 1966-1968
  - Johnson, Rossall J., 1966
  - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1965-1968
  - Johnson, Walter, 1966
  - Johnstone, William D., Jr., 1964-1967
  - Johnstone, L. Craig, 1971
  - Johnstone, William C., 1966
  - Joiner, Charles A., 1965-1970
  - Jones, Gardiner B., 1966
  - Jones, Garth N., 1966
  - Jones, J. Wesley, 1966
  - Jones, Joseph L., 1964-1971
  - Jones, Marshall P., 1965
  - Joshi, A. C., 1967
  - Joyce, Robert P., 1960
  - Judd, Dorothy L., 1965
  - Judd, Walter H., 1963
  - Jung, Clarence, 1963-1971
  - Juniata College, Huntingdon, Pa., 1970-1971
  - Jusuf, General and Mrs. M., 1969
  - Kagan, Sioma, 1970
  - Kahin, George McT., 1963-1972
  - Kahn, Harold L., 1968
  - Kalaidjian, William G., 1959-1965
  - Kalaris, George, 1969
  - Kalb, Bernard, 1966-1971
  - Kalish, Stanley E., 1971
  - Kanahele, George S., 1968
  - Kao, T., undated
  - Kaplan, H. Eliot, 1964-1970
  - Karamoy, Willy A., 1965
  - Kato, Yuichi, 1968
  - Kaufman, Harold J., 1969-1971
  - Keim, S. R., 1966
  - Kekumano, Charles A., 1968
  - Kenda, William, 1968-1969
  - Kennedy, Ethel, undated
  - Kennedy, John F. - Library, Oral History Projects, 1969-1972
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1964
  - Kennedy, Mrs. Stanley C., 1968
  - Kerker, Philip, 1967
  - Khaiser, M. Z., 1967
  - Khosla, J. N., 1965-1966
  - Khouw Bian Tie, 1963-1967
  - Kidder, Randolph A., 1964-1968
  - Kiefer, Alexander F., 1970
  - Kindig, E. B., 1971
  - King, Archie, 1966
  - King, Marian, 1971-1972
  - Kingsley, Mrs. Wm. J., 1971
  - Kirpal, Prem, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Kiyooka, Mrs. Eiichi, 1965-1968
  - Klare, George R., 1967
  - Kleiman, Robert, 1965
  - Kleinjans, Everett, 1970
  - Knebl, F., 1965
  - Knowland, William F., 1970
  - Koch, Henry, 1949
  - Kocher, Eric, 1967-1968
  - Kohler, Foy, 1964
  - Kojima, Kiyoshi, 1968-1971
  - Koontz, Elizabeth D., 1969
  - Korbel, Mr. and Mrs. Alfred, 1965-1966
  - Korten, David, 1971
  - Kosasih, B. E. Anwar, 1965
  - Kothari, Shanti, 1968
  - Krishner, Bernard, 1964-1966
  - Kroeger, Louis J., 1957
  - Kroner, F. R., 1946
  - Krueger, Cliff W., 1967-1969
  - Kruidenier, David, 1971
  - Kruse, Charles C., 1962
  - Kuper, Charles A., 1967
  - Kusuma-Atmadja, M., 1965
  - Kuusisto, Allan A., 1969
  - Kwik, Angie, 1966
  - Lacey, John A., 1964-1965
  - Ladejinsky, Wolf, 1965
  - Laise, Carol C., 1968
  - Lamb, Allan Jackson, 1967
  - Lancaster, Louis, 1968
  - Land, William, 1968
  - Landman, David, 1971
  - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D., 1966
  - Latham, Donald C., 1970
  - Lavan, J. F., 1966
  - Laves, Walter H. C., 1964-1965
  - LaVoie, W. R., 1965-1966
  - Leavey, Ed, 1966
  - Lederer, A. M., 1969
  - Lee, Dorothy M., 1966
  - Lee, Guy A., 1961
  - Lee, Hahn-Been, 1971
  - Lee, Harry A., 1970
  - Lee, Jack C., 1968
  - Leggett, Mr. and Mrs. Allan, 1965
  - Leguebe, Jacques, 1970
  - Leigh, W. Colston, 1961-1969
  - Leishman, Thomas L., 1972
  - Leitenbauer, P. Matth., 1966
  - Lemle, Edna F., 1967-1968
  - Lentzen, T. L., 1964-1965
  - Lenzen, Theodore L., 1967
  - Lenzinger, Carol, 1965
  - Lepawsky, Albert, 1962-1971
  - Lev, Arlene, 1964
  - Lev, Daniel S., 1965-1968
  - Levi, Edward H., 1965
  - Levy, Walter J., 1964-1972
  - Li, Kung Ti, 1965-1966
  - Library of Congress, 1969
  - Liddle, Clifford S., 1969
  - Lie, Edward, 1965
  - Life Magazine, 1968
  - Lightner, E. Allan, Jr., 1968
  - Lilly, P. A., 1969
  - Linch, Sam N., 1965
  - Lindley, Ernest K., 1964-1971
  - Lindquist, Robert S., 1961
  - Lindsey, Jack, 1968-1971
  - Ling, Shen S., 1966
  - Lingenfelder, Laura, 1967
  - Lipkin, Arthur B., 1971
  - Lisle, Robert, 1968
  - Litchfield, Edward H., 1960-1965
  - Litchfield, Mary, 1960-1964
  - Little, Evert T., 1964-1966
  - Little, L. K., 1965-1967
  - Locke, Lucy, 1969
  - Lockhard, Craig A., 1967
  - Lockhart, Frank P., Jr., 1960
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1964
  - Loeffler, Helen, 1968
  - Loewenstein, Mr. and Mrs. Louis, 1967-1969
  - Longyear Historical Society, 1970
  - Lord, Mrs. Everett W., 1966
  - Louchheim, Katie, 1962-1966
  - Love, Marianne, 1962-1964
  - Love, Maryanna, 1962
  - Lowrey, John J., 1966
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - Luce, Henry R., 1966-1967
  - Luhulima, Sonja, 1965-1969
  - Lundberg, N. H., 1966
  - Lyndman, Jack W., 1964-1971
  - Lyon, Cecil B., 1960-1966
  - Lytle, James A., 1971
  - Maarfia, Mohamed, undated
  - McCabe, Robert, 1965
  - McCandless, Lee, 1968-1971
  - Macapagal, Diosadado, 1970
  - McClain, Anita, 1969
  - McClean, John G., 1966-1971
  - McCloy, John J., 1963-1972
  - McConaughy, Walter P., 1966-1970
  - McConough, Patrick J., 1971-1972
  - McCormack, James, 1970
  - McCormick, Charles P., 1960-1966
  - McCoy, Donald Y., 1966
  - McCoy, Gerard L., 1960-1965
  - McCoy, Gilbert E., 1966
  - McCoy, K. Z., 1964-1966
  - McCue, Donald B., 1970
  - McCusker, Paul, 1969-1972
  - McElroy, James T., 1966
  - McElroy, Jesse D., Jr., 1966
  - McFarland, H. F., 1968-1971
  - McGinley, Laurence J., 1966-1970
  - McGraw, Col. W. C., Jr., 1968
  - McInnes, Mrs. Russell, 1971
  - McIntire, Mr. and Mrs. Charles, 1971
  - McIntosh, Edward L., 1968
  - McKay, J. A., 1967
  - McKee, Burtt F., 1966
  - McLellan, Robert, 1969
  - Macmillan Company, 1971
  - McMillan, Sidney L., 1969
  - McMillion, Ovid M., 1965
  - McMullen, Dan D., 1966-1971
  - McMullen, Mrs. Frances, 1968-1972
  - McMullen, J. H., 1964-1966
  - McMullen, Jack L., 1967-1968
  - MacNaughton, Boyd, 1968
  - MacNaughton, Malcolm, 1967-1968
  - Macomber, William B., Jr., 1970
  - MacPherrin, John, 1965-1972
  - McPherson, George H., 1969
  - McQuesten, Fern, 1968
  - Maddox, William P., 1959-1960
  - Magnusson, William L., 1969
  - Mahajani, Usha, 1968
  - Mahony, Walter B., Jr., 1972
  - Makarim, Nono A., 1968
  - Malau, A. S., 1965
  - Malik, Adam, 1967
  - Mallory, Walter H., 1964
  - Malone, Julia T., 1967
  - Malott, Deane W., 1965-1971
  - Malott, Robert H., 1969
  - Maltman, David, 1968
  - Mangkoesasmito, Prawoto, 1960
  - Manglapus, Raul S., 1968
  - Mankind 2000 International, 1968
  - Manley, James C., 1969
  - Manupassa, Leny, 1965-1967
  - Mao Lan-tuan, 1968
  - Maran, Mr., 1968
  - Marble, Eugene S., 1965-1966
  - March, Bob, 1964-1967
  - Marcos, Ferdinand E., 1967
  - Marcus, Aaron G., 1972
  - Mark, Shelley M., 1966
  - Marquis - Who's Who, Inc., 1956-1970
  - Marsh, Harry W., 1965-1971
  - Marshall, A., 1934
  - Marshall, C. B., 1962
  - Marshall-Thomas Co., 1967
  - Martadinata, Mrs., 1966
  - Martens, Robert J., 1965-1966
  - Martin, Edwin W., 1967-1970
  - Martin, Graham, 1966-1967
  - Martin, Harold C., 1971
  - Martokoesoemo, S. B., 1969
  - Masagung, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Mashudi, Kepala, 1966
  - Masland, John W., 1966
  - Mason, John B., 1965
  - Mason, Judith, 1968-1969
  - Masters, Edward, 1966-1970
  - Mathewson, Stephanie, 1965
  - Matlock, Clifford, 1970-1971
  - Matthews, Kenneth, 1969
  - Mau, Edward S. C., 1968
  - Maurer, W., 1969
  - Mautner, Karl, 1964
  - Mayberry, Katherine H., 1962
  - Maynard, David M., 1965-1971
  - Maysenhalder, Ronald, 1969
  - Medeiros, Mrs. Michael, 1972
  - Meeman, Edward J., 1964-1965
  - Mehta, Rama, 1967
  - Mein, George G., 1965
  - Mein, John G., 1959-1964
  - Meissner, Charles, 1965-1968
  - Meissner, Rendall, 1965-1966
  - Meissner, Virginia Ann, 1965-1969
  - Men's Forum Club, 1969
  - Merner, Garfield D., 1965-1972
  - Mertz, Frederic, 1971
  - Mertz, Mrs. R. E., 1964-1972
  - Messegee, Gordon H., 1965-1971
  - Metcalf, W. C., 1969
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970
  - Metzger, Stanley D., 1965
  - Metzke, Erwin J., 1968
  - Meyers, Howard, 1967-1968
  - Meyner, Robert B., 1965
  - Michaelson, J. Leon, 1964
  - Michigan Daily, 1965
  - Midkiff, Frank E., 1968
  - Mifune, Toshiro, 1967
  - Miller, Frank J., 1964-1970
  - Miller, J. D. B., 1964
  - Miller, Paul A., 1968
  - Mills, Mr. and Mrs. Dwight S., 1968-1969
  - Minick, Susan, 1969
  - Mitchell, William F., 1966
  - Miyake, James, 1967
  - Montalvo Association, 1966
  - Montenegro, Daniel W., 1964
  - Monterey Institute of Foreign Studies, 1968
  - Moor, Mr. and Mrs. Edgar J., 1971
  - Moore, F. J., 1964-1968
  - Moore, Frank C., 1949-1970
  - Moore, James A., 1966
  - Moore, Mrs. Persis, 1962
  - Moore, Robert W., 1960-1967
  - Moran, H. O., 1968
  - Morgan, George A., 1965-1970
  - Morgan, Patricia, 1971
  - Moriarity, Gene, 1964
  - Morris, Brewster, 1968-1971
  - Morris, Michael B., 1968-1969
  - Morrissey, F. W., 1965
  - Mott, Rodney L., 1963-1971
  - Moyer, Raymond T., 1970
  - Mueller, Frederick H., 1960
  - Muhammed, Abdullah, 1968
  - Muhtasib, Mohammed A. K., 1962
  - Muller, Steven, 1966
  - Mulligan, Tom, 1965
  - Murfin, Thomas H., 1966
  - Murphy, Robert, 1966
  - Musser, Ruth, 1964-1966
  - Myers, Rowland M., 1968-1969
  - Myra, Allen, 1964
  - Nagy, J., 1970 (Box 14)
  - Nair, K., 1968
  - Nakamura, Edward, 1968
  - Nanna, Lillian, 1965
  - Nasution, Gen. A. H., 1969
  - Nata, A. O. P., 1966-1969
  - Natawidjaja, R. J. S. Rachman, 1967
  - Nathan, Robert R., 1970
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1967-1969
  - National Council for the Social Studies, 1967
  - National Municipal League, 1964-1971
  - National Parks Association, 1965
  - Nature Conservancy, 1968
  - Nau, Alfred, 1966
  - Neilson, N. Paul, 1963
  - Neilson, Paul, 1968
  - Neisser, Walter R., 1966-1971
  - Nelson, George, Jr., 1967
  - Nelson, Robert C., 1972
  - Nelson, Vincent E., 1964
  - Neumann, Peter N., 1970
  - New England Life, 1969-1970
  - New York Times, 1965
  - Newell, James P., 1967-1968
  - Newman, Mrs. Philip F., 1964
  - Niedermeyer, B. E., 1964
  - Nijhoff, Martinus, 1968
  - Nishihara, Kenneth, 1968
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1970-1971
  - Noltin, Frederick E., Jr., 1965
  - North American Aviation - Management Club, Inc., 1965
  - Northwestern University Press, 1966
  - Novogrod, R. J., 1964-1968
  - Nugent, John M., Jr., 1969
  - Nundy, Kaki, 1969
  - Nuuveen, John, 1962-1968
  - Nyack Journal-News, 1965
  - Oakley, Mrs. H. P., 1968
  - Odell, Mr. and Mrs. William R., 1971
  - Oetama, Janey, 1970
  - Okita, Saburo, 1971
  - Okumoto, Peter T., 1968
  - Olds, Dr., 1967
  - Olson, W. A., 1967-1968
  - Oltmans, Willem L., 1970-1972
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1966-1972
  - O'Neill, R. R., 1966
  - Oppenheimer, Fritz, 1966
  - Osborn, David L., 1971
  - O'Sullivan, James L., 1964
  - Oswald, John W., 1965-1967
  - Ota, Charles S., 1968
  - Otis, Elizabeth R., 1963-1970
  - Ourfalian, George, 1965
  - Outrigger Canoe Club, 1967-1969
  - Paauw, Douglas S., 1962-1963
  - Pacific and Asian Affairs Council, 1970
  - Pacific Area Travel Association, 1968
  - Pacific Far East Line, Inc., 1969
  - Pacific Islands Forum, 1966
  - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden, 1966
  - Paget, Roger, 1968-1970
  - Paku Alam VIII, 1961-1962
  - Palar, L. N., 1965-1968
  - Palfrey, Col. Campbell, Jr., 1966
  - Palfrey, John, 1971
  - Palfrey, Thomas R., 1971
  - Palmer, John H., 1972
  - Palmer, Joseph N., II, 1962
  - Palmer, William E., 1965-1967
  - Palmos, Frank, 1969
  - Panglaykim, J., 1965-1966
  - Pant, Apa B., 1962-1970
  - Pao, Johnson Chun-ti, 1967
  - Park, Richard L., 1965-1966
  - Parker, Daniel, 1966
  - Parker, Harrison, 1965-1971
  - Parker, Mack L., 1964
  - Parkhurst, Virginia, 1971
  - Parmer, J. Norman, 1968
  - Parry, Mrs. Marian, 1967-1971
  - Parsons, Howard L., 1964
  - Parsons, J. Graham, 1960
  - Pate, Mrs. Maurice, 1965
  - Paton, Mrs. Sandy, 1969
  - Patterson, Floyd, 1967
  - Pauker, Guy, 1966-1971
  - Paul, Arthur, 1968
  - Pearson, John, 1967
  - Peel, Roy, 1966-1970
  - Pelzer, Karl J., 1966 (Box 15)
  - Penguin Books, Ltd., 1962
  - Penn, Stuart L., 1968
  - Pensa, Paolo, 1965
  - Percy, Charles H., 1967-1972
  - Perkins, Milo, 1968
  - Perry, Russell L., 1968
  - Peters, Richard, 1964
  - Peterson, Avery F., 1965-1966
  - Peterson, Edwin E., 1963-1964
  - Peterson, John R., 1967-1969
  - Petroleum and Trading Corporation, 1963-1969
  - Pfeiffer, William L., 1953
  - Pforzheimer, Carl H., Jr., 1964-1970
  - Phelan, Simmons and Ungar, 1965
  - Phelps, Dudley F., 1964
  - Phelps, Walter W., 1970
  - Philippine-American Press Agency, 1965
  - Philippine National Bank, 1966
  - Pickens, Peter E., 1968
  - Pierson, John H. G., 1967
  - Pifer, Alan, 1971
  - Place, William O., 1968
  - Poch, Tod, 1968
  - Poletti, Charles, 1961-1966
  - Polsky, Anthony, 1968
  - Pond, Elizabeth, 1971
  - Porter, Dwight J., 1964-1968
  - Porter, William J., 1965
  - Potter, Mrs. Ann, 1967
  - Pound, E. Jeanne, 1972
  - Pound, Mrs. W. James, 1971
  - Powers, John, 1966
  - Powers, Joshua B., 1969
  - Prajogo, Consul General, 1967
  - Prawiro, Radius, 1968
  - Preer, Elizabeth, 1962-1969
  - Price, Gwilyam A., 1965
  - Price, Harry B., Jr., 1966
  - Pringle, Robert M., 1970
  - Prochnow, Herbert V., 1962-1968
  - Prud'homme, Hector, 1959
  - Pryor, Millard H., 1964-1965
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1948
  - Puhan, Alfred, 1966-1969
  - Punahou School, 1965
  - Puradindja, Kusna, 1968
  - Purbaja, M. K. A., 1965
  - Purnell, Lewis M., 1965-1972
  - Purukan, Paul, 1971-1972
  - Puspokusumo, G. P. H., 1967
  - Quino, Eduard, 1966
  - Qureshi, Anwar Iqbal, 1966
  - Rabinowitz, Aaron, 1966
  - Radvanyi, Janos, 1972
  - Radway, Fred S., 1963
  - Rahman, Tatiana, 1964
  - Rahman, Tunku Abdul, 1969
  - Rajepakse, Jayanath, 1964
  - Ramnath, J., 1966
  - Ramp, Stephen R., 1967
  - Randall, Clarence B., 1964
  - Rankin, Karl L., 1962-1965
  - Rare Book Company, 1971
  - Rasjid, Harun, 1965
  - Rathvon, Lora C., 1970
  - Raupe, Craig, 1965
  - Razak, Abdul, 1968
  - Re, Edward D., 1968
  - Read, Mr. and Mrs. John B., 1970
  - Read, Nicholas C., 1970
  - Reader's Digest, 1961-1963
  - Reischauer, Edwin O., 1964-1971
  - Rendall, John L., 1970
  - Rendall, Judy, 1971
  - Rendall, Leonard, undated
  - Rendall, Willard J., 1965-1966
  - Rennie, William R., 1971
  - Renz, Dora, 1967
  - Research to Prevent Blindness, Inc., 1966-1969
  - Reyes, Narciso, 1962-1972
  - Rhatigan, Margie, 1967
  - Rice, Edward E., 1966-1967
  - Rice, John S., 1962
  - Rich, Robert G., Jr., 1969
  - Richards, Florence S., 1961-1969
  - Richardson, Kenneth, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Richardson, Virginia, 1965-1967
  - Richardson, William S., 1966-1968
  - Richter, Anne, 1969
  - Rickart, Nancy, 1965
  - Ricks College, Rexburg, Idaho, 1968
  - Riddleberger, James W., 1970
  - Riggs, Barbara, 1968-1969
  - Riggs National Bank, Washington, D.C., 1962
  - Rightor, C. E., 1962-1968
  - Riley, Herb, 1970
  - Riley, Lawson H., 1965-1966
  - Rinden, Robert W., 1965
  - Risson, Arnold, 1964
  - Roberts, Chalmers M., 1963-1971
  - Robertson, Walter S., 1962-1968
  - Robey, King, 1967
  - Robinson, Gilbert A., 1972
  - Robinson, Hamlin, 1965-1966
  - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1962-1968
  - Rockefeller, John D., IV, 1964-1970
  - Rodrigoes, John S., 1965
  - Rogers, Lindsay, 1964
  - Rohrer, Mrs. Grant, 1962-1965
  - Rollins, Harry T., 1963
  - Romulo, Carlos P., 1966
  - Roney, Don, 1969
  - Rooney, John J., 1968
  - Roosman, Raden S., 1966
  - Rose, Elizabeth H., 1968-1969
  - Roseman, Alvin, 1964
  - Rosen, Herman P., 1968
  - Rosenbaum, Samuel R., 1962
  - Rosene, Mrs. B. N., 1968
  - Rosengren, Col., 1968
  - Rosner, Dan, 1966
  - Rostow, Walt W., 1963
  - Roth, William M., 1968
  - Rountree, William M., 1962-1971
  - Roush, Carroll J., 1970
  - Routt, Garland C., 1966
  - Rowland, Genevieve, 1965
  - Rubottom, Roy R., 1962-1970
  - Rudinger, Lillian, 1966-1968
  - Rusk, Dean, 1965
  - Rusk, Eleanor J., 1969
  - Russell, Francis H., 1965
  - Russell, Hilda, 1964-1966
  - Russell, Mary F., 1960
  - Rutherford, M. R., 1962-1963
  - Ryan, Guy, 1968
  - Ryan, John D., 1968
  - Ryerson, Knowles A., 1965
  - Sadik, Achmad, 1962
  - Sadikin, Ali, 1969
  - Sahib, Sonja M., 1969
  - Salen, Elly, 1962
  - Sammartino, Peter, 1962
  - Samson, Henry T., 1963-1964
  - Sanders, Sol W., 1966
  - Santoso, Mrs. Sri H., 1965-1966
  - Sarjadi, Soegeng, 1965-1967
  - Sartono, 1962-1969
  - Sastraatmadja, 1967-1968
  - Sastroamidjojo, Ali, 1969
  - Saturday Review, 1966-1967
  - Sauell, Isabelle R., undated
  - Saunders, John B. deC. M., 1964
  - Scalapino, Robert A., 1963-1966
  - Schaleben, Arville, 1971
  - Schmidt, Hannah, 1969
  - Schmitt, Gerhard, 1960
  - Schneidman, Harold F., 1967
  - Schoenbrun, David F., 1967-1970
  - Schroeder, Celia T., 1969-1970
  - Schwartz, Louis, Jr., 1964
  - Schweidler, Irene, 1965
  - Schweitzer, Pierre-Paul, 1967
  - Sebald, William, 1961-1970
  - Seed, Allen H., Jr., 1966
  - Seeley, Paul S., 1967
  - Seidman, J. S., 1963-1970
  - Selby, R. W., 1962
  - Selective Service System, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1968
  - Selkirk, 1963
  - Selznick, Miriam R., 1971
  - Sen, Sudhir, 1965-1967
  - Senu, A., 1967
  - Service, Richard, 1964
  - Shann, K. C. O., 1964
  - Shaplen, Robert, 1969
  - Sharma, Narendra P., 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Sharp, Adm. U. S. G., Jr., 1964-1965
  - Sharpe, Blanche W., 1970
  - Shaw, Carroll K., 1967-1968
  - Shaw, Patrick, 1964-1967
  - Sheaves, R. S., 1968
  - Shenfield, Hale, 1965
  - Sherrod, Robert, 1967
  - Shields, Thomas, 1967
  - Shinoda, Minoru, 1966-1969
  - Shoemaker, James, 1965
  - Shute, Ben, 1966
  - Siagian, Sabam, 1966
  - Sie Pek Ho, 1967
  - Siffin, William J., 1960-1967
  - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1970-1971
  - Simmons, Robert G., 1955
  - Simon, Milton, 1969-1972
  - Simon, Sheldon W., 1970
  - Simonetti, Thomas, 1966
  - Sinclair, Gregg M., 1965-1968
  - Singer, Russell E., 1969-1970
  - Singh, Jasdip, 1969
  - Singh, L. P., 1966-1968
  - Sitompul, Bernhard, 1965
  - Sjarif Thajeb, 1971
  - Skole, Guenter, 1964
  - Skolnik, Olga, 1946-1969
  - Slowinski, Walter A., 1967
  - Smiley, Joseph R., 1968
  - Smith, Adele M., 1971
  - Smith, Mr. and Mrs. Datus C., Jr., 1968-1972
  - Smith, E. P., Jr., 1965
  - Smith, Edward C., 1965-1970
  - Smith, George F., 1968
  - Smith, H. Alexander, 1962-1965
  - Smith, Horace H., 1965-1967
  - Smith, James H., 1972
  - Smith, Karen H., 1971
  - Smith, N. J., 1967
  - Smith, Nolle R., 1965
  - Smith, Ray W., 1971
  - Smith, Col. Robert M., 1968
  - Smith, Mrs. Theo. C., 1969
  - Smith, Walker W., 1962
  - Smyser, A. A., 1965-1967
  - Smyth, Frances S., 1965-1972
  - Sneider, Richard L., 1968
  - Snowden, George W., 1966
  - Snyder, Richard E., 1963
  - Soebchan, M., 1965
  - Soedjatmoko, 1964-1970
  - Soegondho, 1968
  - Soenarjo, Inc. J., 1967
  - Soetisno, Chandra D., 1968
  - Soewargana, Oejeng, 1965-1970
  - Sokol, Anthony E., 1967
  - Solomon, George, 1964
  - Sons in Retirement, 1969
  - Sorensen, Wendy, 1962-1965
  - Southard, Frank A., Jr., 1965-1967
  - Spaulding, William E., 1971-1972
  - Spigler, Donald S., 1964
  - Spinks, Charles N., 1965-1967
  - Spoehr, Alexander, 1965-1966
  - Sprat Bay Club, Inc., St. Thomas, V. I., 1963
  - Sprouse, Philip D., 1966
  - Stahl, O. Glenn, 1968
  - Standard Oil Company, 1966-1969
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1968
  - Starobin, Joseph R., 1968
  - State of Hawaii, 1968
  - State - USIA Recreation Association, Inc., 1970
  - Stauffer, John N., 1969-1971
  - Stebbins, Henry E., 1966
  - Stedman, Adelaide, 1969-1971
  - Stedman, Louise A., 1964
  - Steeves, John M., 1964-1972
  - Steinberg, David, 1965
  - Steiner, Arthur H., 1965
  - Steinhauser, Samuel S., 1970
  - Stevens, Mr. and Mrs. M. J., 1971
  - Stevenson, William E., 1962-1970
  - Stewart, E. E., 1969
  - Stewart, James L., 1971
  - Stewart, Paul A., 1970
  - Stiller, Helene, 1969
  - Stinnes, Margiana, 1971
  - Stoessel, Fredric, 1972
  - Stoessel, Walter J., Jr., 1964
  - Stoffer, Dr., 1969
  - Stokely, Hugh L., Jr., 1965
  - Stoker, Emory D., 1964
  - Stone, Donald C., 1949-1967
  - Straus, Robert K., 1971
  - Stroh, A. H., 1962-1967
  - Strombeck, Natalie, 1969
  - Strout, Richard L., 1971 (Box 18)
  - Student Center Foundation, 1965
  - Stutesman, John H., Jr., 1959
  - Subandrio, Dr., 1965
  - Subardjo, Ahmad, 1969-1970
  - Subroto, Mrs. Gatot, 1969
  - Sudhir Sen, 1965
  - Sudiarso, Iravati, 1965-1966
  - Sudiasih, Oka, 1969
  - Sukarno, 1958-1966
  - Sukarno, Ratna Sari Dewi, 1965-1967
  - Sukawati, Jjokorda, 1968
  - Sullivan, Charles A., 1965
  - Sullivan, William H., 1960
  - Sumitro, 1968
  - Suparsono, Mrs. S. A., 1970-1971
  - Suprapto, R. Hadi, 1969
  - Surwargana, Oejeng, 1964
  - Susanto, Markus, 1968
  - Sutadji, Ari, 1969
  - Sutijipto, Maj. Gen., 1968
  - Sutikno Lukitodisastro, 1969
  - Sutjipto, Danukusumo, 1965
  - Sutomo, 1959
  - Suwarto, 1966
  - Swaminathan, Sri Lata, 1970
  - Swearingen, Roger, 1965
  - Sweetland, Monroe, 1962-1969
  - Swett, Douglas B., 1968
  - Swisher, Capt., 1946
  - Swiren, Mr. and Mrs. Max, 1968-1969
  - Sworakowski, Witold, 1968
  - Sycip, W., 1966
  - Tahapary, Dary, 1967
  - Tahija, Julius, 1962-1969
  - Tan, Mr. and Mrs. Kok H., 1965-1967
  - Tan, Tjin Kie, 1966
  - Tangkilisan, Mr. and Mrs. P. M., 1963-1971
  - Tanguy, Charles R., 1968
  - Tanimoto, R. Brian, 1971-1972
  - Taubenblatt, Selig A., 1969
  - Taylor, Carl, 1965-1966
  - Taylor, Harold, 1966-1967
  - Taylor, Maurice F. W., 1964
  - Taylor, Gen. Maxwell D., 1962-1972
  - Tejera, Paris, 1971
  - Temple, A. L., 1966
  - Temple of Understanding, Inc., 1968-1969
  - Tenney, Edward V., 1969
  - Terrel, Charles L., 1968
  - Terry, Helen, 1968-1971
  - Thajeb, Sjarif, 1962
  - Thauer, Falak, 1967
  - Thé, Robert, 1967
  - Thomas, Paul F., 1967
  - Thomas, Reuben R., 1965
  - Thompson, E. N., 1965-1972
  - Thompson, Meg, 1964-1967
  - Thompson, Milton S., 1964
  - Thomson, James C., Jr., 1966
  - Thorngren, Mrs. Dale, 1966
  - Thull, Beulah, 1955-1970